Clyp Privacy Policy
===================

SOCIAL

Clyp Privacy Policy
===================

Information We Collect
----------------------

There is certain information that we collect automatically as the result of your use of Clyp or through the use of cookies and other web analytics services. This information generally includes:

**Usage Information** - We collect information about your interactions with the Clyp, including the pages that you visit and links you click on, streaming, uploading, connecting your Facebook account, sharing an audio file with another user, following or unfollowing another user, posting a comment, performing a search, the time, frequency and duration of your visits, and whether you interact with email messages, for example, if you opened, clicked on, or forwarded the email message.

**Log Data** - We automatically collect log information when you use Clyp, even if you have not registered for an account or logged in. That information includes, among other things: details about how you've used Clyp (including links to third party sites or services), Internet Protocol (IP) address, access times, your browser type and operating system, device information, device event information (e.g., crashes, browser type), and the page you've viewed or engaged with before or after using Clyp.

**Cookies** - We use cookies and other similar technologies, such as pixels, local storage, and mobile device identifiers and may also allow our business partners to use these tracking technologies on Clyp, or engage others to track your behavior on our behalf.

**Location Data** - When you use certain features on Clyp, we may collect data about your general location (e.g. IP address). Most mobile devices allow you to control or disable the use of location services for applications in the device's settings.

**Device Information** - We collect information from and about the devices you use, including how you interact with Clyp and information about the device itself, such as the hardware model, operating system, IP addresses, cookie information, device settings, mobile carrier information, mobile device and advertising identifiers, apps installed, browser type, language, battery level and time zone. Apple's iOS Advertising Identifier (IDFA) and Google's Android Advertising ID are examples of device identifiers.

**Deleting Your Account** - If you have an account and would like to delete it, you may do so by sending an email with your profile URL and the email address associated with your account to this email address: [delete@clyp.it](mailto:delete@clyp.it) If you delete your account, all data associated with your account, including the audio files that you have uploaded and the usage data associated with those audio files, will be deleted. Even if you delete your Clyp account, it is possible that your information may still show up in some internet search results for a short while afterwards, if the search engine maintains a temporary cache of web pages. Search engines' caching processes are outside of Clyp's control and therefore we cannot be responsible for any information that remains cached by search engines after that information has been removed from Clyp. Please note that deleting any Clyp Apps, or any third party apps to which your Clyp account is connected, will not delete your Clyp account. Similarly, if you delete a third party app that is connected to your Clyp account over our API, this will not necessarily delete all data about your Clyp activity from within that third party app. You will need to refer to the app provider's terms of use and privacy policy to find out how to delete data about your Clyp activity from that third party app.

**Data Deletion Request Process** - If you wish to request the deletion of your data, please send an email request to [delete@clyp.it](mailto:delete@clyp.it) with the subject line: "Data Deletion Request". In the body of the email, provide your profile URL and the email address associated with your Clyp account. Once your request is received, we will process it as promptly as possible. All data associated with your account, including audio files uploaded and usage data related to those files, will be deleted. It is important to be aware that deleted information may temporarily appear in internet search results if search engines have cached web pages. This caching process is beyond Clyp's control. Deleting Clyp Apps or third-party apps connected to your Clyp account will not automatically delete your Clyp account. If you wish to delete data about your Clyp activity from third-party apps, please refer to the respective app provider's terms of use and privacy policy. By following these steps, you can ensure that your data is removed from our systems in compliance with your request. If you have any further questions or need assistance, please contact our support team at [support@clyp.it](mailto:support@clyp.it).

Purposes of Information We Collect
----------------------------------

We use this automatically collected data to determine the popularity and usefulness of various features, to analyze how our site is used so as to keep it optimized, and to maintain the integrity of user accounts so that each user can see their Clyps and the comments associated with them.

We also use such data to enable us to comply with copyright law and to respond to lawful requests by public authorities, including national security, courts, and law enforcement.

We partner with third party advertisers who may use cookies to collect data about which pages and ads are viewed while our site is being used. Advertiser cookies enable customized ads that are selected for display on your device based on anonymous information collected. No personal data is on, connected to, or derivable from, these cookies. If you block or disable cookies and other tracking technologies, instead of getting customized ads you will see non-customized ads.

Upload

Sign Up

Log In

* 
* You don't have any notifications.

* Upload
* Profile
* Settings
* Sign Up
* Log In
* Log Out

Made with love in Austin, TX.

© 2024 Clyp, Inc. All rights reserved.

Sign up with Facebook

or

 Tell me about Clyp news

By signing up, I agree to Clyp's [Terms of Service](https://clyp.it/terms) and [Privacy Policy](https://clyp.it/privacy).

Already have an account? [Log in](#)

Log in with Facebook

or

 Remember me [Forgot password?](#)

Don't have an account? [Sign up](#)

#### Reset Password

Enter the email address associated with your account, and we'll email you a link to reset your password.

A link to reset your password has been sent to , if that account exists. The link will expire in 20 minutes.

Send verification email Done

Processing ...

Drop in an audio file or click to upload

Try again

Cancel

By uploading you agree to our [Terms](https://clyp.it/terms)

Upload failed

Upload successful!
------------------

#### Copy the link below to share your Clyp

By recording you agree to our [Terms](https://clyp.it/terms)

Discard Upload

Cancel

Try again

Record something else
